Get health insurance before the age of 30 years, it will be
cheaper for you and you will incur less, then when will you get
health insurance?
Whenever you go to do all this work,
take the premium, then do not
ask him, small premiums are monthly, big
premiums are yearly, understood, get
health insurance before the age of 30 years, it will be
cheaper, will it be
cheaper, for example, if we get our health insurance, it will be a
little cheaper, if we get our mother and father's
health insurance, the company will charge expensive, will the premium be
expensive, because they know that these people have become old, they will
fall sick more,
we know that brother, we are going to fall sick less,
here you people will incur less,
you people are younger and you will incur less, so the
company is seeing that brother, the company's
income is the premium and if we ask for a claim, then the
company will incur an expense, so an old
person will ask for more claim on health and what about us, generally
see, there is no age for illness,
but generally the
expectation that you people have in young age is
less, so when will you get health insurance,
when will you people get your  When you get a job etc.
then eat your fill now, there is no problem, don't indulge
in drama here
that you should eat fruits or bread, you should
not do all this, you should
work honestly and whoever is eating too much bread and
biscuits, fight with the village boy and
take away his money, he will take out all his
butter and jam,
yes, he will take out pizza and burger and will beat them
like chowmein,
never indulge in all this, eat your fill and
work honestly, there is no problem, if you
understand then you understand insurance,
now we will move on to the banking account, sir, the
premium of insurance can be monthly or
yearly, well there is a duration of premium, for
how long it has to be paid, if it has to be paid for
life, then some say
that it has to be paid for 5 years, some insurance covers
10 years, now all these are the
conditions, how much premium has to be paid, whether it has to be paid monthly
or yearly, for how many years it has to be paid,
after which year you will start
getting the benefit, like this, pay the first premium and
start getting the benefit, then  All the
conditions are written in it, did you understand it
or not? Whenever you go to do all this work and
take the premium, do not ask him what
benefits you will get, you should ask what all you will not
get. A man had taken insurance. This is an
incident from Kanpur or Lucknow and he formed a
society. There will be no insurance claim in the society.
He had also said that he should
marry off his sister with the insurance money of the society and he jumped in front of a train.
This incident happened seven or six years ago.
Now the insurance company has
rejected the insurance. Does it mean that if a
person continues to form a society like that, and the
government also says that it will not be for the society members, because
this will increase crime. Suppose
someone adopts an orphan child, gets it
insured, appoints himself as his successor,
kills him and
says that he has committed suicide. Now
give him the money. The rules are
made after thinking deeply. Did you understand it or not?
Now, in case of insurance suicide, the
company will sink
everything. Now there are some such premiums
which also cover the society. If you commit
suicide, it will be fine. So what will happen when the person who
comes to investigate will do it.  No, he will
first see whether the person is going to commit suicide or not,
like
Yamraj will talk to me in a few minutes, I will get him admitted
in the foundation batch, give him a few minutes,
see, the biology batch is really cool, the
batch is on 27th, we
will teach you the skeleton system, it is really amazing, we will
teach you immediately after showing you everything.